http://www.scene.co.nz/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We want you to be aware of our Internet Privacy Policy because information about users can be collected via our website. You should note the terms and conditions applying to this information. Our Privacy Statement discloses the information we collect, how we use it, and how you may correct or alter it. Detailed information on the New Zealand Privacy Act is available from http://privacy.org.nz.
Gathering of information:
Apart from news information (see below), Mountain Scene Ltd (“we” or “us”) may gather two types of information about you (“you”):
(a) Personal details and information provided by you when registering for our services or participating in online surveys; and
(b) Aggregated information not related to you personally but gathered by our systems or by third party systems tracking our site traffic.
You, of course, have the right not to answer personal-information questions but this may mean you are not entitled to access some of our services.
Information disclosure:
We may disclose: (a) All information we gather, including your personal information, to Mountain Scene Ltd and related companies;
(b) Merged tracking information and other information that will not personally identify you to third parties including advertisers and partners;
(c) Your personal information to third parties provided we believe in good faith that the law obliges us to do so; (d) And your personal information to third parties in any other circumstances, strictly subject to having first obtained a clearance from you to do so when collecting such information.
Use:
Your personal information gathered by us will enable us to:
(a) Confirm your identity should you forget password or login details required for our registration-only services;
(b) Take online credit card purchases from you;
(c) Provide additional services you may request;
(d) Forward information about you to other websites and services which we believe will be of interest to you;
(e) Approach you for future marketing, promotional and publicity purposes, including direct marketing, market research and surveys;
(f) Offer you access to advertising and other information streamed for its direct relevance to you and your interests; and
(g) Put such information to any other use you may authorise.
Cookies and Tracking:
We may use a cookie file containing information to identify your computer. This information is limited, giving details only of your IP address, PC platform (Windows, NT or Mac), Browser (eg. Microsoft, Netscape or other, plus the version of Browser) and domain (whether accessing the site from NZ or elsewhere). We may use this information to:
(a) Track traffic patterns to, from and within our site, to gain knowledge such as (but not limited to) which pages you most like to visit, how long you spend on each page, each visit’s date and time, and which pages were viewed first and last;
(b) Stream advertising to selected target market groups and, conversely, prevent certain advertising being viewable to certain other groups; and
(c) Offer you special member access without you having to log on each time or to visit members-only sections of the site.
You have the choice of turning cookies off in your browser and/or deleting them from your hard drive. They need not be turned on to use our website but you may need them for future areas of the site under development. If cookies are turned off, we are unable to control the frequency of certain accompanying advertising. This could become annoying.
Advertisers, Content Providers and Partners, Third Party Ad Servers
Site advertisers, content providers and partners are wholly independent of us. So are Third Party Ad Servers used by some of our advertisers to deliver promotional messages to you via our site. The content and conduct of all such groups above are completely outside our control. You may be asked by them to provide personal information while on our site or using some of our services or links. Please be aware these third parties may not follow the same privacy policies we do: we urge you to check their practices before giving any information out to third parties.
In or Out
On our website, you have a choice: “Opt In” or “Opt Out”. If our plans to collect, use or disclose your personal information are outside those stated in this Privacy Policy, we will give you the option to:
(a) Opt Out and not receive certain services or participate in certain interactive areas; or
(b) Opt In by, for example, consenting to allow us to offer you special promotions or new website features.
Google Analytics – www.google.com/analytics
Google Analytics’ website measurement software and system helps track site traffic patterns and gathers collective, anonymous information about visits. We use the system to find out certain statistics such as, for example, the number of pages viewed, the number of unique visitors, how long visitors spend on the site, and common entry and exit points into and from the website. This non-personal information is collated by Google to assist in our analysis. All our web pages carry a small piece of hidden Google Analytics code. The software stores a cookie in your browser (if you have enabled cookies) with a unique identifier to track the number of unique visitors. Information collated by Google Analytics cannot identify you personally and no personal information is stored. For more, see the Privacy Policy on www.google.com/analytics
Privacy Policy Amendments
We retain the right to amend this policy at any time by notifying users that a revised Privacy Policy has been published on our site.
News information – our Privacy Policy does not apply:
Our Privacy Policy does not apply to information gathered by Mountain Scene in relation to its news activities, whether those activities culminate in publication on line, in the print edition of Mountain Scene, or not.
Holding, Correcting, Updating
Personal information provided to us will be collected and held at Level 1, 10 Athol Street, Queenstown, New Zealand. Under the Privacy Act 1993, you have the right to access and correct personal information held by us about you. Corrections or changes will be made as often as necessary. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or how it works, please email webmaster@scene.co.nz or contact us by mail to Mountain Scene Ltd, Level 1, 10 Athol Street, Queenstown, New Zealand.
Advertisement
The South
Today
Queenstown
Toggle Dropdown
The South
Made with the support of NZ On AirPage 1 of 1
The South
